so the question is my wife my individual
wine and it's funny actually for me it
was very pragmatic I've been thinking
about I'm trying to figure out how to
address a set of challenges that
humanity is facing and going to be
facing over the next up a decade for
these 15 years in the process of doing
that I happen to encounter again he was
thinking about lovely same things
and you're trying to figure out how he
and I might be able to coordinate as
soon as approach my approach I'm afraid
to the direction and he mentioned Ricky
and his brother James has been
collaborating on a applied neuroscience
company it was interesting because the
nice thing with recent proof is in the
pudding I could just try that they move
into makes me find out whether or not
they're doing
I'll help me useful so I did and he was
interesting is worked
I took the what we're now calling qualia
and it was called version 1 1 1 7 or
something ok nerdy back then and I was
actually a little bit astounded by how
effectively it worked the clarity
focused because it kind of flow through
and make quick decision I guess most
importantly be the emotional resilient
was very powerful frankly if you
actually spend time with some deeply
into reality what we're collectively
facing it can be quite emotionally
overwhelming I think most people shy
away from look into it clearly because
revolution everyone and and so for me
this was actually getting on to notes
the first was just at an individual
level the increase in my own personal
capacity to do something that I've been
deeply invested in for
app is very powerful so I wanted to help
but then ii was realizing that this is
the kind of thing that scale you can
turn this into artifact a product then
you can get it out to millions of people
and millions of people up listed in some
sustainable predictable way it's very
powerful I might be able to go out have
personal conversations we have a hundred
people and I might be able to write
things click it out to hundreds of
thousands of people very lightly but if
you can get millions of people
significally upgrade their capacity to
contemplate the worlds in the
perspective that they're occupying what
if they are specifically to do and be
able to actually respond to that
possibly most powerful up the fabric
this is the sort of thing that no one or
small group of us is actually going to
be able to solve if the sort of thing is
going to require a collective
intelligence store that I've been
telling